Leke Abiodun

Full-stack Developer

lekepeterabiodun@gmail.com

https://lekeabiodun.com

+234 706 2427 397

Nigeria.

Summary

I love writing codes that solve unique problems and create solutions that drive business growth, I'm a performance-driven and motivated Full-Stack Developer. I have experience working with large-scale systems, and have built highly responsive websites and web applications. I have 4+ years of practical knowledge in PHP/Laravel/Livewire, WordPress, JavaScript/AlpineJS, Bootstrap/TailwindCSS. I'm currently learning VueJS for single-page applications (SPA) and hybrid mobile apps.

Work Experience

IT Assistant at Lagos State University.

Nigeria - Jun 2015 - Dec 2015

- Developed a WordPress-based eCommerce store.
- Developed a WordPress-based blog site.

Freelance WordPress Developer at WebSolutionsDublin.

Ireland - Feb 2017 - Oct 2018

- Design and development of multiple business websites.
- Design and development of landing pages for WebSolutionsDublin and clients.
- Developed a web scraper to automate most part of the data collection in the company CRM.
- Created a few videos for marketing and promotions.

Full-stack Developer at AppTech Solutions.

Nigeria -Oct 2018 - September 2021

- Developed several modules for the in-house design of a school management system using PHP/Laravel.
- Developed a recruitment exercise job portal.
- Developed Human Resource Management System.
- Created multiple website templates.

Freelance PHP/Laravel Developer at GetServ.

India -March 2020 - Feb 2021

- Developed customer service chatbot using Laravel.
- Developed an interface to connect with WhatsApp chat API.
- Integrated the Chat-bot backend with WhatsApp chat API with WhatsApp account.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Adekunle Ajasin University of Akungba: 2012

- Relevant Coursework:

OperatingSystems, Architecture, Linux/Unix Programming, Usability in Website and Software Design. C,C++,C#, Java FORTRAN, Python Programming,Relational Database Design & SQL, Compiler construction.

Professional Certification in Project Management

Obafemi Awolowo University: 2017 - 2018.

My tools

- Editors: Sublime, VScode.
- Frameworks: Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, WordPress, Laravel, VueJS.
- Libraries: JQuery, Alpine, Laravel-Livewire.
- Languages: JavaScript, PHP, Python, MQL5.
- Database: MySQL.
- Version Control System: GIT.
- Project Management: Trello, Github.
- Testing Frameworks: PESTPHP, Cypress.

Personal skills

- Good human skills, teamwork.
- Fast learning, self-motivated.
- Analytical and precise in dealings with issues.
- Verbal and written in English.
- Conduct effective meetings using SCRUM.
- Google-Fu (I can search my way out of most technical problems).